Senh Yeung

7 Perronet House, Princess Street, London SE1 6JR 07584468726

senh.yeung@gmail.com

Personal Profile

I am a Cisco Certified Network Associate, with knowledge in network routing and switching - currently studying towards CCNP. I have experience working in a NOC and Datacenter environment as a 24/7 shift NOC support Engineer with a proven ability to adapt to new challenges and providing professional network diagnostic capabilities and fault resolution for LAN, WAN and Wireless technologies.

Work Experience

NOC Support Engineer (24/7 shift) - KDDI Europe (Mar 2019 - present)

Main achievements: Providing key ticket management with KDDI's VIP clients, in a joint liaison with vendors, carriers, third-parties and SI Engineers to troubleshoot and carry out technical tasks to assist in the recovery of critical circuits, in a professional and timely manner.

- Customer focused support from fault inception to resolution and adhering to best practices involving key updates to clients and resolving incidences with relevant parties, internal and external and closing 10-12 tickets daily.
- Experienced with level 3 operational support for incidences relating to both IT and Network services, including remote hands-on support for our client's servers at KDDI/Telehouse Data center.
- Providing support and troubleshooting CPE/Core configurations, port configurations, IP address
 assignment and similar activities allocated from provisioning Team with a strong emphasis and
 understanding of EIGRP, BGP, OSPF, MPLS, site to site VPN, Ipsec VPN and Silverpeak SDWAN technologies.
- Utilisation of network management tools (Solarwinds, Cisco Prime, Nagios, OpManager) to monitor incidences and providing key data for troubleshooting incidences.
- Experience and practical knowledge for switches, routers and firewalls for many varied vendors (Cisco, Juniper Palo Alto etc)
- Visiting customer sites to provide initial support and installation of company devices for smaller clients.
- Providing Ad-hoc tasks such as client tape changes, system administrations and monthly reports for our VIP clients.

IT Support Administrator - OCS Consulting (Dec 2018 - Feb 2019)

Main achievements: Providing Customer focused support, from ticket management to troubleshooting with developers and resolving 8-10 tickets daily. Adhering to best business practices involving updating support documentations, sharing knowledge and providing feedback to improve business procedures.

- Experienced with MS SQL and Oracle database.
- Providing first point of contact for Clients, ensuring all tickets have been logged, assessed and managed in a timely manner.
 - Gathering necessary data from clients and carrying out initial analysis for troubleshooting and resolving cases.
 - Escalating critical/time-sensitive tickets with developers and providing assistance to troubleshoot and resolve urgent technical cases.
 - Proactively tracking tickets and ensuring visibility to clients with timely updates.
- Processing daily client system checks and reporting failures to relevant teams. Scheduling backup procedures and monitoring system archives/logs for errors.
- Interrogating Business Databases using SQL to provide business performance reports for senior consultants and line managers.

Finance & Application Support - ChoiceSupport (May 2016 - June 2018)

Main achievements: Provided AR solutions utilising VBA and Powershell scripts to streamline external processes into the new system's bespoke module and ensuring accurate invoicing and income allocations.

- Experienced with OpenAccounts, eBis, Dashboard, V1 and Collaborative Planning.
- System admin for all OneAdvanced Finance Applications.
- Responsible for the development of Intuitive Dashboard and building KPI components to key budget holders/SMT members and devised reconciliation processes to ensure data accuracy.

- Responsible for further eBis development to update existing forms as per new specifications and helped set up the subsidiary company, LVT into eBis.
- Provided technical support and solutions to ongoing development needs in Finance.
- Responsible for auto payments in AR and providing general AR training to other members of Finance.
- Assist Finance Managers with importing data using the OAsystem's modules to efficiently
 update settings for all areas in OpenAccounts system.

Account Assistant - Fintech Company, Payleven Ltd (July 2014 - April 2016)

Main achievements: Managed numerous projects to implement VBA solutions to improve efficiency and accuracy for Accounts receivable / allocation processes.

- Experienced with Twinfield Accounting Software & Dynamic NAV
- Working with the Finance Director and Cosmo Consulting to create and import Rapidstart Migration packages for the new ERP system, Dynamic NAV.
 - o Mapping customer / supplier accounts, AR/AP transactions & opening balances.
 - Journals & closing balance for chartered ledgers
- Lead the Online Amazon outlet project, working with Logistics and building a system to account for the revenue and fees into Twinfield and Dynamic NAV.
- Responsible for Accounts Receivables
 - Liaising with other departments including Logistics and company Holding to reconcile monthly stock reconciliation / reseller invoices / credit notes.
 - This includes receiving Megaventory reports and extensive excel use to create a mailmerge solution and further Macro scripts to generate the pdf & word doc. automatically.
- Processing Purchase invoices and allocating them to their respective department.
- Handling Merchant's gueries and reconciling their payment on our online Merchant platform

Education & Qualification

2019 Silverpeak

SD-WAN Professional

2018 **Cisco**

CCNA Routing & Switching

2015 - 2017 **AAT**

Part Level 2 Qualification

2003 – 2006 Westminster Kingsway College

3 A Level's: Mathematics(B), Physics(B), ICT (B) 2 AS Level's: Computing(B), Electronics(C)

1998 – 2003 Geoffery Chaucer Secondary school

GCSE's: 11 A - C

GNVQ: ICT. Awarded Pass

Skills

Language: Cantonese (conversational)

Technical Skills:

- Proficient Networks Routing & Switching (Network Topologies, LAN Switching, Network Management, TCP/IP troubleshooting, Routing Protocols, MPLS and SD-WAN)
- Proficient Microsoft SQL/ Oracle Database
- Proficient VBA, Python and Powershell
- Proficient Excel user (Vlooksups, pivot tables, etc.)
- Excellent knowledge of computer hardware and software
- Proficient Microsoft Office user

Accounting Software Packages:

- Advance Open Accounts / Dashboard / eBis / Collaborative Planning
- Microsoft Dynamic NAV

References

Available on request